[
    {
        "front": "To rest, sit, or sleep on a perch",
        "back": "roost"
    },
    {
        "front": "A small jeweled crown worn by women",
        "back": "tiara"
    },
    {
        "front": "To wrinkle the face in displeasure; frown",
        "back": "scowl"
    },
    {
        "front": "A system of interconnectin paths; a maze",
        "back": "labyrinth"
    },
    {
        "front": "Relating to cooking or the kitchen",
        "back": "culinary"
    },
    {
        "front": "A brother or sister",
        "back": "sibling"
    },
    {
        "front": "Of great size or range",
        "back": "vast"
    },
    {
        "front": "Hung from above",
        "back": "suspended"
    },
    {
        "front": "Fixed in place by cables or the like",
        "back": "moored"
    },
    {
        "front": "Artificial or imitation; fake",
        "back": "faux"
    }
]